[
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Japan?",
        "correct": "Tokyo",
        "wrong1": "Yakutsi",
        "wrong2": "Arimato",
        "wrong3": "Sakura"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who became the Japanese emperor in 2019?",
        "correct": "Naruhito",
        "wrong1": "Sakura",
        "wrong2": "Shinta",
        "wrong3": "Kawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which currency is in use in Japan?",
        "correct": "Yen",
        "wrong1": "Arimato",
        "wrong2": "Dollars",
        "wrong3": "Euro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sakura?",
        "correct": "Cherry Blossom",
        "wrong1": "Dress",
        "wrong2": "Mountain",
        "wrong3": "Religion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Japan is the third biggest economy in the world. After which two countries?",
        "correct": "USA and China",
        "wrong1": "Russia and USA",
        "wrong2": "China and England",
        "wrong3": "England and Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two colours are on the flag of Japan?",
        "correct": "Red and White",
        "wrong1": "Blue and Green",
        "wrong2": "Black and Orange",
        "wrong3": "Yellow and Purple"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest Japanese island?",
        "correct": "Honshu",
        "wrong1": "Kyushu",
        "wrong2": "Hokkaido",
        "wrong3": "Shikoku"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Japan's name in Japanese?",
        "correct": "Nippon",
        "wrong1": "Sika",
        "wrong2": "Hokkaido",
        "wrong3": "Shinano"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the traditional dress of Japan?",
        "correct": "The Kimono",
        "wrong1": "The Kawaii",
        "wrong2": "The Kaishodo",
        "wrong3": "The Kominai"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which volcano erupted in 1707?",
        "correct": "Mount Fuji",
        "wrong1": "Mount Yoko",
        "wrong2": "Mount Ayumi",
        "wrong3": "Mount Hamasaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the current population of Japan?",
        "correct": "125.8 million",
        "wrong1": "1.32 hundred million",
        "wrong2": "208.3 million",
        "wrong3": "207.3 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 'Shinto'?",
        "correct": "A religion",
        "wrong1": "Moutain",
        "wrong2": "Dress",
        "wrong3": "Cherry Blossom"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most popular western nickname for Japan?",
        "correct": "Land of the Rising Sun",
        "wrong1": "Land of the Long White Cloud",
        "wrong2": "Land of the Tornados",
        "wrong3": "Land of the Green Dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the population of Tokyo?",
        "correct": "13.96 million",
        "wrong1": "145.3 hundred thousand",
        "wrong2": "23.32 million",
        "wrong3": "9.98 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of deer is also known as the spotted deer or the Japanese deer?",
        "correct": "Sika Deer",
        "wrong1": "Suka Deer",
        "wrong2": "Soki Deer",
        "wrong3": "Siku Deer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Kinkaku-ji?",
        "correct": "A Temple",
        "wrong1": "A Religion",
        "wrong2": "A Weave",
        "wrong3": "A Flower"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the other name given to the Japanese macaque?",
        "correct": "Snow Monkey",
        "wrong1": "Gilled Swan",
        "wrong2": "Devils Spider",
        "wrong3": "Dusted Macaw"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city can you find Godzilla Road?",
        "correct": "Tokyo",
        "wrong1": "Kyoto",
        "wrong2": "Osaka",
        "wrong3": "Hiroshima"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the culture of cuteness in Japan called?",
        "correct": "Kawaii",
        "wrong1": "Kinkaku-ji",
        "wrong2": "Atatakai",
        "wrong3": "Denwa"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you are taking the fastest train from Tokyo to Osaka, how long will it take?",
        "correct": "2hrs 30mins",
        "wrong1": "2hrs",
        "wrong2": "1hr",
        "wrong3": "1hr 15mins"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest river in Japan?",
        "correct": "Shinano River",
        "wrong1": "Bishoujo River",
        "wrong2": "Futago River",
        "wrong3": "Ichiban River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which famous Japanese woman was married to John Lennon?",
        "correct": "Yoko Ono",
        "wrong1": "Donarudo toranpu",
        "wrong2": "Ka Hon",
        "wrong3": "Kawaii Getsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many samurai are there in the 1954 movie '_______ Samurai'",
        "correct": "Seven",
        "wrong1": "Twenty",
        "wrong2": "Three",
        "wrong3": "One"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Pok√©mon an abbreviation for in Japan?",
        "correct": "Pocket Monsters",
        "wrong1": "Peace Makers",
        "wrong2": "Little Devils",
        "wrong3": "Tamed Fighters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of series is 'Erased'?",
        "correct": "A manga",
        "wrong1": "An anime",
        "wrong2": "A movie",
        "wrong3": "A comic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first emperor of Japan?",
        "correct": "Jimmu Tenno",
        "wrong1": "Tempura Sako",
        "wrong2": "Kyoto Ay",
        "wrong3": "Koy Saki"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which side was Japan in WWI?",
        "correct": "Allies",
        "wrong1": "Axis",
        "wrong2": "Alliance",
        "wrong3": "Attackers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US military based was attack by Japan during WWII?",
        "correct": "Pearl Harbor",
        "wrong1": "Diamond Cove",
        "wrong2": "Emerald Beach",
        "wrong3": "Ruby Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which side was Japan in WWII?",
        "correct": "Axis",
        "wrong1": "Allies",
        "wrong2": "Alliance",
        "wrong3": "Attackers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital of Japan before Tokyo?",
        "correct": "Kyoto",
        "wrong1": "Hiroshima",
        "wrong2": "Osaka",
        "wrong3": "Nagoya"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did Japan become a member of the United Nations?",
        "correct": "1956",
        "wrong1": "1899",
        "wrong2": "1912",
        "wrong3": "1943"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two Japanese cities were bombed by the US in 1945?",
        "correct": "Hiroshima and Nagasaki",
        "wrong1": "Tokyo and Osaka",
        "wrong2": "Hiroshima and Tokyo",
        "wrong3": "Nagasaki and Osaka"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of meat are Kobe and Wagyu?",
        "correct": "Beef",
        "wrong1": "Chicken",
        "wrong2": "Lamb",
        "wrong3": "Pork"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Japanese dish consists of food battered and deep fried?",
        "correct": "Tempura",
        "wrong1": "Kaminari",
        "wrong2": "Oni",
        "wrong3": "Kuragari"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which meat is used to make Yakitori?",
        "correct": "Chicken",
        "wrong1": "Beef",
        "wrong2": "Pork",
        "wrong3": "Lamb"
    },
    {
        "question": "What broth is used to make Miso Soup?",
        "correct": "Dashi",
        "wrong1": "Moku",
        "wrong2": "Mizu",
        "wrong3": "Sui"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Donburi mean in Japanese?",
        "correct": "Bowl",
        "wrong1": "Plate",
        "wrong2": "Tea",
        "wrong3": "Cup"
    },
    {
        "question": "Iwama Ryu, Iwama Shin Shin Aiki Shuren Kai are all forms of which Japanese martial art?",
        "correct": "Aikido",
        "wrong1": "Taichi",
        "wrong2": "Karate",
        "wrong3": "Nagano"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city can you find the Universal Studios in Japan?",
        "correct": "Osaka",
        "wrong1": "Tokya",
        "wrong2": "Hiroshima",
        "wrong3": "Nagano"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Shinkansen?",
        "correct": "High-speed train",
        "wrong1": "Figure skating",
        "wrong2": "Religion",
        "wrong3": "Market"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times has Tokyo hosted the Summer Olympics?",
        "correct": "Twice",
        "wrong1": "Nonce",
        "wrong2": "Once",
        "wrong3": "Thrice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport is Naomi Osaka known for?",
        "correct": "Tennis",
        "wrong1": "Figure skating",
        "wrong2": "Baseball",
        "wrong3": "Football"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport is Ichiro Suzuki known for?",
        "correct": "Baseball",
        "wrong1": "Figure skating",
        "wrong2": "Tennis",
        "wrong3": "Football"
    }
]